<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Constellations</string>
    <string name="aquarius_horo">You might have to accept that this isn\'t a day for getting lots done. Couch naps may call your name and it\'ll be all too easy to put things off. Happily, there are probably at least a few things on today\'s list that can wait until tomorrow for your attention. Figure out which ones need to be finished right away and get them done as soon as possible. Once you\'re free, you can kick back and relax as much as you want!</string>
    <string name="pisces_horo">Chattering pals might bore you almost to tears today. This could be especially irritating if you were hoping for a bit of peace and quiet. Still, these people are likely your friends for a reason. Try to have patience with any tedious conversations until you can politely disengage. Then you can take some time to enjoy being in your own space! You may want to spend a few hours reflecting on your next move any actual movement can wait until tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="aries_horo">Someone might grate on your nerves by demanding one thing after another from you. While they may be entitled to ask things of you, you\'re allowed to ignore them and pay attention to your own life instead. You may have to simply shrug your shoulders and get on with things. On the other hand, spending a bit of your time with old and comfortable friends can add some cheer to your day without weighing you down underneath any unnecessary burdens.</string>
    <string name="taurus_horo">Dealing with people who don\'t see the world in the same way as you can be tiring right now, it might be downright stressful. Happily, all you need to do today is be prepared to ask if there\'s something going on that you don\'t understand. People might not realize you need any help unless you ask, so saying something the moment you feel lost is a good idea. A small amount of effort now could save you a lot of grief later!</string>
    <string name="gemini_horo">A little bit of self-indulgence shouldn\'t do you any harm right now. In fact, it may help you feel better able to face the world. The key thing is to keep it only to a little bit! Getting carried away could make it difficult to get anything else done. If you need help motivating yourself, think about why you want to do the things that you\'re doing. It may take a while to find the answers, but the questions are worth asking.</string>
    <string name="cancer_horo">You may be too concerned about manipulation from friends at the moment. It\'s possible that you\'re blaming others for cramping your style when you\'ve done all the cramping yourself! Consider taking a close look at the ties that bind you to see if there are better approaches. You may be worried that if you let someone take an inch, they\'ll take a mile. In reality, it\'s more likely that your loved ones or peers will offer you some of their inches in return.</string>
    <string name="leo_horo">Currently, people could seem to lack respect for your boundaries. It may feel like they\'re calling in favors solely to be a nuisance! That said, you might need to consider the idea that their requests are reasonable you\'re just tired. Even if doing anything feels exhausting, you should make an effort to ensure you at least cover what you promised. A commitment\'s a commitment! Once you\'ve dealt with any necessary tasks, you can get back to relaxing and recharging.</string>
    <string name="virgo_horo">Having fun might seem to involve far too much hard work, right now! It\'s OK to hit pause on a hobby if you aren\'t enjoying yourself. Plus, you can take this time to get some work done on other things. When it comes to your daily tasks, there is probably plenty of help available as long as you politely tell people when you need it. Today is a day for being practical and making space for the fun that will come again later.</string>
    <string name="libra_horo">Domestic obligations can be tiresome today, perhaps even completely cramping your style. In fact, you might start to wonder if you have a style at all! There\'s no point in moping about and moaning. Maybe there isn\'t as much fun and excitement on offer as you\'d like, but that doesn\'t mean you need to completely write off today. It\'s OK not to be happy all the time feel free to show your true feelings as you get things done in whatever way you can.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_horo">You could be distracted by countless people requesting favors from you right now. Fortunately, you don\'t have to say yes just because someone asks. You don\'t have to say no to everything either, but it\'s fair to pick and choose. Your best option is to do your best to work out whether you have enough free time and enthusiasm for the task. If not, you might be able to pass it on to someone close to you who could actually help.</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_horo">A bit of retail therapy might be quite fun today, but throwing money at anything that bothers you may not solve any underlying issues. In fact, it could bring about more problems later. The solution? Take an extra moment today to ensure that the spending you have in mind is a good idea. Sometimes it is, sometimes it isn\'t. As long as you don\'t impulsively buy everything that strikes your fancy, you can probably avoid landing yourself in any serious financial bother.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_horo">An offer that sounds wonderful could have some strings attached at this time. That doesn\'t have to be a problem if you\'re aware of those strings and happy to accept them, but make sure you have the full picture first. Taking the easy way out by simply saying yes could lead to plenty of regrets. Don\'t be too worried about refusing if someone has assumed you\'ll go along with what they want without even asking you, that\'s their problem, not yours!</string>
</resources>